cloud4wi.com 2016-10-06

# Privacy Policy - Cloud4Wi

## PRIVACY POLICY

Last Updated: November 3, 2015

This Privacy Policy (this “Policy”) describes how Cloud4Wi Inc. (“Cloud4Wi” and “we”) handles the information of individuals who (“you” and “your”) visit the site www.cloud4wi.com (“Site”).

**DEFINITIONS**  
When used in this Agreement, the following terms shall have the respective meanings indicated, such meanings to be applicable to both the singular and plural forms of the terms defined:

“Personal Data” or “Data” means any information regarding a natural person, a legal person, an institution or an association, which is, or can be, identified, even indirectly, by reference to any other information, including a personal identification number.  
“Usage Data” means information collected automatically from this Site, which can include: the IP addresses or domain names of the computers utilized by the Users who use this Site, the URI addresses (Uniform Resource Identifier), the time of the request, the method utilized to submit the request to the server, the size of the file received in response, the numerical code indicating the status of the server’s answer (successful outcome, error, etc.), the country of origin, the features of the browser and the operating system utilized by the User, the various time details per visit (e.g., the time spent on each page within the Site) and the details about the path followed within the Site with special reference to the sequence of pages visited, and other parameters about the device operating system and/or the User’s IT environment.  
“User” means the individual using this Site, which must coincide with or be authorized by the legal or natural person to whom the Personal Data refers.

**TYPES OF DATA COLLECTED**  
Among the types of Personal Data that this Site collects, by itself or through third parties, there are: Cookie, Usage data, First Name, Last Name, Phone Number, Company Name, Job Title, Country, Email address, Geographic Position and Various types of Data. Other Personal Data collected may be described in other sections of this Policy or by dedicated explanation text contextually with the Data collection.  
This Site may track Users by storing a unique identifier of their device, for analytics purposes or for storing Users’ preferences.  
The Personal Data may be freely provided by the User, or collected automatically when using this Site.  
Any use of Cookies – or of other tracking tools – by this Site, unless stated otherwise, serves to identify Users and remember their preferences, for the sole purpose of providing the service required by the User.  
For operation and maintenance purposes, this Site and any third party services may collect files that record interaction with this Site (System Logs) or use for this purpose other Personal Data (such as IP Address).  
Failure to provide certain Personal Data may make it impossible for this Site to provide its services.  
Users are responsible for any Personal Data of third parties obtained, published or shared through this Site and confirm that they have the third party’s consent to provide the Data to Cloud4Wi.

**COOKIES**  
This Site uses Cookies. To learn more and for a detailed cookie notice, you may consult the Cookie Policy.

**HOW WE USE YOUR PERSONAL DATA**  
The Personal Data collected are used to provide the User with services or to sell goods, including payment and possible delivery. The Personal Data collected to complete the payment may include the credit card, the bank account used for the transfer, or any other means of payment envisaged. The kind of Data collected by this Site depends on the payment system used.  
Personal Data is collected also for the following purposes: Analytics, Contacting the User, Content performance and features testing (A/B testing), Displaying content from external platforms, Handling payments, Hosting and backend infrastructure, Interaction with external social networks and platforms, Interaction with support and feedback platforms, Location-based interactions, Managing contacts and sending messages, Managing support and contact requests, Registration and authentication, Remarketing and Behavioral Targeting, Social features, SPAM protection and User database management.

**ANALYTICS**  
The services contained in this section enable Cloud4Wi to monitor and analyze web traffic and can be used to keep track of User behavior.  
Alexa Metrics (Alexa Internet, Inc.) : Alexa Metrics is an analytics service provided by Alexa Internet, Inc. Personal Data collected: Cookie and Usage data. Place of processing: USA – [Privacy Policy](http://www.alexa.com/help/privacy) – [Opt Out ](http://www.alexa.com/settings/optout)

Analytics collected directly (This Site) : This Site uses an internal analytics system that does not involve third parties.  
Personal Data collected: Cookie and Usage data.

Facebook Ads conversion tracking (Facebook, Inc.) : Facebook Ads conversion tracking is an analytics service provided by Facebook, Inc. that connects data from the Facebook advertising network with actions performed on this Site.  
Personal Data collected: Cookie and Usage data.  
Place of processing: USA – [Privacy Policy ](https://www.facebook.com/about/privacy/)

Google Analytics (Google Inc.) : Google Analytics is a web analysis service provided by Google Inc. (“Google”). Google utilizes the Data collected to track and examine the use of this Site, to prepare reports on its activities and share them with other Google services. Google may use the Data collected to contextualize and personalize the ads of its own advertising network.  
Personal Data collected: Cookie and Usage data.  
Place of processing: USA – [Privacy Policy](http://www.google.com/intl/en/policies/privacy/) – [Opt Out](http://tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout?hl=en)

Google AdWords conversion tracking (Google Inc.) : Google AdWords conversion tracking is an analytics service provided by Google Inc. that connects data from the Google AdWords advertising network with actions performed on this Site.  
Personal Data collected: Cookie and Usage data.  
Place of processing: USA – [Privacy Policy ](http://www.google.com/intl/en/policies/privacy/)

Google Tag Manager (Google Inc.)  
Google Tag Manager is an analytics service provided by Google Inc.  
Personal Data collected: Cookie and Usage data.  
Place of processing: USA – [Privacy Policy ](http://www.google.com/intl/en/policies/privacy/)

HubSpot Analytics (HubSpot, Inc.) : HubSpot Analytics is an analytics service provided by HubSpot, Inc.  
Personal Data collected: Cookie and Usage data.  
Place of processing: USA – [Privacy Policy](https://www.hubspot.com/legal/privacy-policy) – [Opt Out ](mailto:privacy@hubspot.com)

WordPress Stats (Automattic Inc.) : WordPress Stats is an analytics service provided by Automattic Inc. Personal Data collected: Cookie and Usage data. Place of processing: USA – [Privacy Policy ](http://automattic.com/privacy/)

**CONTACTING THE USER**  
Contact form (This Site) : By filling in the contact form with their Data, the User authorizes this Site to use these details to reply to requests for information, quotes or any other kind of request as indicated by the form’s header. Personal Data collected: Company name, Country, Email address, First Name, Last Name, Phone number, Job Title.  
Mailing List or Newsletter (This Site): By registering on the mailing list or for the newsletter, the User’s email address will be added to the contact list of those who may receive email messages containing information of commercial or promotional nature concerning this Site. Your email address might also be added to this list as a result of signing up to this Site or after making a purchase. Personal Data collected: Email address.  
Phone contact (This Site) : Users that provided their phone number might be contacted for commercial or promotional purposes related to this Site, as well as for fulfilling support requests. Personal Data collected: Phone number.

**CONTENT PERFORMANCE AND FEATURES TESTING (A/B TESTING)**  
The services contained in this section allow the Owner to track and analyze the User response concerning web traffic or behavior regarding changes to the structure, text or any other component of this Site.  
Google Website Optimizer (Google Inc.): Google Website Optimizer is an A/B testing service provided by Google Inc. Google may use Personal Data to contextualize and personalize the ads of its own advertising network.  
Personal Data collected: Cookie and Usage data.  
Place of processing: USA – [Privacy Policy ](http://www.google.com/intl/en/policies/privacy/)

**DISPLAYING CONTENT FROM EXTERNAL PLATFORMS**  
These services allow you to view content hosted on external platforms directly from the pages of this Site and interact with them. If a service of this kind is installed, it may still collect web traffic data for the pages where the service is installed, even when users do not use it.

Google Fonts (Google Inc.) : Google Fonts is a typeface visualization service provided by Google Inc. that allows this Site to incorporate content of this kind on its pages.  
Personal Data collected: Usage data and Various types of Data as specified in the privacy policy of the service.  
Place of processing: USA – [Privacy Policy ](http://www.google.it/intl/en/policies/privacy/)

Google Maps widget (Google Inc.): Google Maps is a maps visualization service provided by Google Inc. that allows this Site to incorporate content of this kind on its pages.  
Personal Data collected: Cookie and Usage data.  
Place of processing: USA – [Privacy Policy ](http://www.google.it/intl/en/policies/privacy/)

Gravatar (Automattic Inc.) : Gravatar is an image visualization service provided by Automattic Inc. that allows this Site to incorporate content of this kind on its pages. Please note that if Gravatar images are used for comment forms, the commenter’s email address or parts of it may be sent to Gravatar – even if the commenter has not signed up for that service.  
Personal Data collected: Email address and Usage data.  
Place of processing: USA – [Privacy Policy  
](http://automattic.com/privacy/)  
Vimeo video (Vimeo, LLC) : Vimeo is a video content visualization service provided by Vimeo, LLC that allows this Site to incorporate content of this kind on its pages.  
Personal Data collected: Cookie and Usage data.  
Place of processing: USA – [Privacy Policy  
](http://vimeo.com/privacy)  
Youtube video widget (Google Inc.) : Youtube is a video content visualization service provided by Google Inc. that allows this Site to incorporate content of this kind on its pages.  
Personal Data collected: Cookie and Usage data.  
Place of processing: USA – [Privacy Policy ](http://www.google.it/intl/en/policies/privacy/)

Typekit (Adobe Systems Incorporated) : Typekit is a typeface visualization service provided by Adobe Systems Incorporated that allows this Site to incorporate content of this kind on its pages.  
Personal Data collected: .  
Place of processing: USA – [Privacy Policy ](http://www.adobe.com/privacy/typekit.html)

**HANDLING PAYMENTS**  
Payment processing services enable this Site to process payments by credit card, bank transfer or other means. To ensure greater security, this Site shares only the information necessary to execute the transaction with the financial intermediaries handling the transaction. Some of these services may also enable the sending of timed messages to the User, such as emails containing invoices or notifications concerning the payment.

PayPal (PayPal Inc.) : PayPal is a payment service provided by PayPal Inc., which allows Users to make online payments using their PayPal credentials.  
Personal Data collected: Various types of Data as specified in the privacy policy of the service.  

Stripe (Stripe Inc) : Stripe is a payment service provided by Stripe Inc.  
Personal Data collected: Various types of Data as specified in the privacy policy of the service.  
Place of processing: USA – [Privacy Policy ](https://stripe.com/terms/US)

**HOSTING AND BACKEND INFRASTRUCTURE**  
These services have the purpose of hosting data and files that enable this Site to run and be distributed as well as to provide a ready-made infrastructure to run specific features or parts of this Site. Some of these services work through geographically distributed servers, making it difficult to determine the actual location where the Personal Data are stored.

Amazon Web Services (Amazon) : Amazon Web Services is a hosting service provided by Amazon.com Inc.  
Personal  
Data collected: Various types of Data as specified in the privacy policy of the service.  

**INTERACTION WITH EXTERNAL SOCIAL NETWORKS AND PLATFORMS**  
These services allow interaction with social networks or other external platforms directly from the pages of this Site. The interaction and information obtained by this Site are always subject to the User’s privacy settings for each social network. If a service enabling interaction with social networks is installed it may still collect traffic data for the pages where the service is installed, even when Users do not use it.  
Facebook Like button and social widgets (Facebook, Inc.) : The Facebook Like button and social widgets are services allowing interaction with the Facebook social network provided by Facebook, Inc.  
Personal Data collected: Cookie and Usage data.  
Place of processing: USA – [Privacy Policy ](http://www.facebook.com/privacy/explanation.php)

Paypal button and widgets (PayPal Inc.) : The PayPal button and widgets are services allowing interaction with the PayPal platform provided by PayPal Inc.  
Personal Data collected: Cookie and Usage data.  
Place of processing: See the PayPal privacy policy –[Privacy Policy ](https://www.paypal.com/cgi-bin/webscr?cmd=p/gen/ua/policy_privacy-outside)

Pinterest “Pin it” button and social widgets (Pinterest): The Pinterest “Pin it” button and social widgets are services allowing interaction with the Pinterest platform provided by Pinterest Inc.  
Personal Data collected: Cookie and Usage data.  
Place of processing: USA – [Privacy Policy ](http://about.pinterest.com/privacy/)

ShareThis (Sharethis Inc.) : ShareThis is a service provided by ShareThis Inc., which displays a widget that allows interaction with social networks and external platforms as well as sharing the contents of this Site. Depending on the configuration, this service can display widgets belonging to third parties such as the managers of social networks where interactions are shared. In this case, also the third parties that provide the widget will be informed of interactions and Usage Data on the pages where this service is installed.  
Personal Data collected: Cookie and Usage data.  
Place of processing: USA – [Privacy Policy ](http://sharethis.com/privacy)

Twitter Tweet button and social widgets (Twitter, Inc.) : The Twitter Tweet button and social widgets are services allowing interaction with the Twitter social network provided by Twitter, Inc.  
Personal Data collected: Cookie and Usage data.  
Place of processing: USA – [Privacy Policy  
](http://twitter.com/privacy)  
Google+ +1 button and social widgets (Google Inc.) : The Google+ +1 button and social widgets are services allowing interaction with the Google+ social network provided by Google Inc.  
Personal Data collected: Cookie and Usage data.  
Place of processing: USA – [Privacy Policy  
](http://www.google.com/intl/en/policies/privacy/)  
Linkedin button and social widgets (LinkedIn Corporation) : The Linkedin button and social widgets are services allowing interaction with the Linkedin social network provided by LinkedIn Corporation. Personal Data collected: Cookie and Usage data. Place of processing: USA – [Privacy Policy ](https://www.linkedin.com/legal/privacy-policy).

**INTERACTION WITH SUPPORT AND FEEDBACK PLATFORMS**  
These services allow Users to interact with third party support and feedback platforms directly from the pages of this Site. If one of these services is installed, it may collect browsing and Usage Data in the pages where it is installed, even if the Users do not actively use the service.

Zendesk Widget (Zendesk) : The Zendesk Widget is a service for interacting with the Zendesk support and feedback platform provided by Zendesk Inc.  
Personal Data collected: Cookie and Usage data.  
Place of processing: USA – [Privacy Policy ](http://www.zendesk.com/company/privacy)

**LOCATION-BASED INTERACTIONS**  
Non-continuous geolocation (This Site): This Site may collect, use, and share User location Data in order to provide location-based services.  
Most browsers and devices provide tools to opt out from this feature by default. If explicit authorization has been provided, the User’s location data may be tracked by this Site.  
The geographic location of the User is determined in a manner that isn’t continuous, either at the specific request of the User or when the User doesn’t point out their current location in the appropriate field and allows the Site to detect the position automatically.  
Personal Data collected: Geographic position.

**MANAGING CONTACTS AND SENDING MESSAGES**  
These services make it possible to manage a database of email contacts, phone contacts or any other contact information to communicate with the User. These services may also collect data concerning the date and time when the message was viewed by the User, as well as when the User interacted with it, such as by clicking on links included in the message.

Mailchimp (Mailchimp) : Mailchimp is an email address management and message sending service provided by Mailchimp Inc.  
Personal Data collected: Email address.  
Place of processing: USA – [Privacy Policy  
](http://mailchimp.com/legal/privacy/)  
HubSpot Email (HubSpot, Inc.): HubSpot Email is an email address management and message sending service provided by HubSpot, Inc.  
Personal Data collected: Email address and Usage data.  
Place of processing: USA – [Privacy Policy ](https://www.hubspot.com/legal/privacy-policy)

**MANAGING SUPPORT AND CONTACT REQUESTS**  
These services allow this Site to manage support and contact requests received via email or by other means, such as the contact form. The Personal Data processed depend on the information provided by the User in the messages and the means used for communication (e.g. email address).

Zendesk (Zendesk) : Zendesk is a support and contact request management service provided by Zendesk Inc.  
Personal Data collected: Various types of Data as specified in the privacy policy of the service.  
Place of processing: USA – [Privacy Policy ](http://www.zendesk.com/company/privacy)

**REMARKETING AND BEHAVIORAL TARGETING**  
These services allow this Site and its partners to inform, optimize and serve advertising based on past use of this Site by the User. This activity is performed by tracking Usage Data and by using Cookies, information that is transferred to the partners that manage the remarketing and behavioral targeting activity.

AdWords Remarketing (Google Inc.): AdWords Remarketing is a Remarketing and Behavioral Targeting service provided by Google Inc. that connects the activity of this Site with the Adwords advertising network and the Doubleclick Cookie.  
Personal Data collected: Cookie and Usage data.  
Place of processing: USA – [Privacy Policy](http://www.google.com/intl/en/policies/privacy/) – [Opt Out ](http://www.google.com/settings/ads/onweb/optout)

**SOCIAL FEATURES**  
Inviting and suggesting friends (This Site) : This Site may use the Personal Data provided to allow Users to invite their friends – for example through the address book, if access has been provided – and to suggest friends or connections inside it.  
Personal Data collected: Various types of Data.

**SPAM PROTECTION**  
These services analyze the traffic of this Site, potentially containing Users’ Personal Data, with the purpose of filtering it from parts of traffic, messages and content that are recognized as SPAM.

Google reCAPTCHA (Google Inc.) : Google reCAPTCHA is a SPAM protection service provided by Google Inc.  
Personal Data collected: Cookie and Usage data.  
Place of processing: USA – [Privacy Policy  
](https://www.google.com/intl/policies/privacy/)  
Akismet (Automattic Inc.): Akismet is a SPAM protection service provided by Automattic Inc.  
Personal Data collected: Various types of Data as specified in the privacy policy of the service.  
Place of processing: USA – [Privacy Policy ](http://automattic.com/privacy/)

**USER DATABASE MANAGEMENT**  
These services allow Cloud4Wi to build user profiles by starting from an email address, a personal name, or other information that the User provides to this Site, as well as to track User activities through analytics features. This Personal Data may also be matched with publicly available information about the User (such as social networks’ profiles) and used to build private profiles that the Owner can display and use for improving this Site.  
Some of these services may also enable the sending of timed messages to the User, such as emails based on specific actions performed on this Site.

HubSpot CRM (HubSpot, Inc.): HubSpot CRM is a User database management service provided by HubSpot, Inc.  
Personal Data collected: Email address, Phone number and Various types of Data as specified in the privacy policy of the service.  
Place of processing: USA – [Privacy Policy  
](https://www.hubspot.com/legal/privacy-policy)  
HubSpot Lead Management (HubSpot, Inc.) : HubSpot Lead Management is a User database management service provided by HubSpot, Inc.  
Personal Data collected: Various types of Data as specified in the privacy policy of the service.  
Place of processing: USA – [Privacy Policy  
](https://www.hubspot.com/legal/privacy-policy)  
Pipedrive (Pipedrive OÜ) : Pipedrive is a User database management service provided by Pipedrive OÜ.  
Personal Data collected: Various types of Data as specified in the privacy policy of the service.  
Place of processing: Estonia – [Privacy Policy ](https://www.pipedrive.com/en-US/privacy)

**WHO WE SHARE YOUR PERSONAL DATA WITH**  
In addition to Cloud4Wi, in some cases, the Data may be accessible to certain types of persons in charge, involved with the operation of the site (administration, sales, marketing, legal, system administration) or external parties (such as third party technical service providers, mail carriers, hosting providers, IT companies, communications agencies). The updated list of these parties may be requested from Cloud4Wi at any time.

**WHERE WE STORE YOUR PERSONAL DATA**  
The Data is processed at Cloud4Wi’s operating offices and in any other places where the parties involved with the processing are located. For further information, please contact Cloud4Wi.

**HOW LONG WE RETAIN YOUR PERSONAL DATA**  
The Data is kept for the time necessary to provide the service requested by the User, or stated by the purposes outlined in this document, and the User can always request that Cloud4Wi suspend or remove the data.

**SECURITY MEASURES WE USE**  
Cloud4Wi processes the Data of Users in a proper manner and shall take appropriate security measures to prevent unauthorized access, disclosure, modification, or unauthorized destruction of the Data. The Data processing is carried out using computers and/or IT enabled tools, following organizational procedures and modes strictly related to the purposes indicated.

**PRIVACY POLICY FOR CHILDREN**  
We do not knowingly collect information from anyone under the age of 13 unless we first obtain permission from that child’s parent or legal guardian. If we learn that we have collected information from a child under the age of 13 on the Site, we will delete that information as quickly as possible.  
If you become aware that your child has provided us with Personal Data without your consent, please contact us at [privacy@cloud4wi.com](mailto:privacy@cloud4wi.com).

**ACCESS TO YOUR PERSONAL DATA**  
If you wish to access, correct, or delete the information about you, you may submit a request to [privacy@cloud4wi.com](mailto:privacy@cloud4wi.com). If you provide us with sufficient information to identify you and verify your identity, we will use reasonable efforts to comply with your request.

**AMENDMENTS TO THIS POLICY**  
Cloud4Wi reserves the right to make changes to this Policy at any time by giving notice to its Users on this page. It is strongly recommended to check this page often, referring to the date of the last modification listed at the top. If a User objects to any of the changes to the Policy, the User must cease using this Site and can request that Cloud4Wi removes the Personal Data. Unless stated otherwise, the then-current Policy applies to all Personal Data Cloud4Wi has about Users.

**LEGAL INFORMATION**  
The User’s Personal Data may be used for legal purposes by Cloud4Wi, in Court or in the stages leading to possible legal action arising from improper use of this Site or the related services. The User declares to be aware that Cloud4Wi may be required to reveal personal data upon request of public authorities.  
Notice to European Users: This Policy has been prepared in fulfillment of the obligations under Art. 10 of EC Directive n. 95/46/EC, and under the provisions of Directive 2002/58/EC, as revised by Directive 2009/136/EC, on the subject of Cookies.

**CONTACTS**  
If you have any questions or comments about this Policy, please contact Cloud4Wi using the following contact information:

Cloud4Wi Inc.  
363 Clementina Street  
San Francisco, 94103, California  
United States of America
